

Blert Anadolli

Web designer/developer and Graphic Designer

+38349883532

■ blertana05@gmail.com

★ https://blert.netlify.app/

Peje, Kosove

SUMMARY

I'm an advanced website designer and developer who worked with many different brands and companies. I have experience with more than 4 years in website industry, starting from designing the website to developing it using database. I'm also compatible with using Adobe Photoshop and less with Premiere Pro. Also I manage social medias.

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer, Graphic Designer and Social Media management

11/2020 - Present

Penaltia

Created, hosted and managed the website of Penalia portal. Started from scratch and built using Wordpress. Also designed the company logo and still managing their social medias.

Web Developer 01/2021 - 01/2022

LIGSport

Created, hosted and managed the website of LIGSport portal. Started from scratch and built using Wordpress. You can check the website using this link: https://ligsport.net

Web Developer 04/2020 - 02/2022

Radio Taxi Beka

Created, hosted and managed the website of a taxi company in Peja. Started from scratch and built using html, css, js and also using NodeJS and database.

EDUCATION

Computeric Sciences 2022

Bedri Pejani

High School Diploma

Completed the high school on Computeric Sciences field

CERTIFICATES

jCoders course 06/2018 - Present

SKILLS

Website DesignAdvancedSocial Media ManagementIntermediateGraphic DesignAdvancedLogo DesignIntermediate

LANGUAGES